hey guys Jason from kellyco I'm here
today with Debbie from my lab when we're
looking over the mine lab equinox metal
detector if you're somebody that enjoys
metal detecting then you know how
important it is to be able to hear all
the sounds that your detector makes
that's why we wear headphones a lot of
the time so one of the great features
about these machines are the headphones
and Debbie do tell us a little bit about
that
sure well with the 800 you get a variety
of options you get these aptX slowly you
see bluetooth headphones and what that
does is it allows the coil to pass over
their target and send you that
information as quickly as possible
without any way you can also plug these
headphones in directly or it also comes
with the wide stream box which even cuts
the latency down more wow so you have a
lot of options now you said the 600
comes with wired headphones and the 800
comes with the wireless headphones right
that's correct but both machines can
still perform all three styles that's
correct well that's really amazing I'll
tell you what this is one of the most
important features to have because sound
as that comes into play a big time when
you're out there looking for treasure
go to our website Kelly cocom you can
find out some more information and until
next time happy hunting